Morning Ashish, today of course sir, Q3 results
season will kick off. TCS numbers will
come in the evening but some Q3 updates have also come. The
market will keep an
eye on that too in the early trade today. Titan,
where the company said that on an average, the
combined sales growth of all the standard on business has been
around 12% in this quarter. There has been an
increase of about 11% in jewellery devices.
22 new stores have been
added here. The demand for studded jewellery is more than gold
jewellery which is plain gold jewellery. There has been an
increase of 14% in this segment. They added 48 new stores. There has been a
growth of 10% in the IK segment. 36 new stores have been
added and there has been a growth of up to 75% in the emerging business as well.
Overall, 111
new stores have been added in the third quarter.
This update has come from the company.
Now we will focus on Bandhan Bank. There has been an
increase of about 14% in advances. So, year-on-quarter growth of
only 5%.  There is an increase in deposit growth. There has been a
good annual TV. There are
positive
losses on a yearly basis and 8% losses
on a quarterly basis. Retail deposits have increased by
two to three percent. You have
seen a very good yearly growth in book deposits up
to 140%, but quarterly
pressure has been seen, so the
performance of Bandhan Bank will be on average in the third quarter.
Tata Steel's Q3
update also came, where we are talking about an increase of
about four percent in India business production.
India business delivery on a quarterly basis, however, has
decreased by 4%. On a Kautilya basis, it has been seen
increasing by 7% on an annual basis. The production in the European business has
decreased on a quarterly basis, a decline of up to 6% was
seen, although there has been an
increase in business delivery there. So
this is about Tata Steel. Along with this,
you will also keep some insurance companies
on the radar, where the premium
of the overall industry in December has been seen increasing by 14%.
Early year to date, there has been an
increase of 16% in debt premium.
ICICI Lombard has
gained market share here, the market share
came around 8.5%, in December the
premium accounted for up to 9%, year to date there was an increase of 21%,
in New India Assurance, there has been a
decline of up to 2% in the premium in December, they have lost market share,
they have lost market share of about 220 points,
now their market share has
come down slightly to 14% and if you talk about Star Health,
there too the market share has increased a
little on this point but
in December premiums there has been an increase of about 16%,
for that if you look at it closely then the
best performance of such loans has been recorded,
an update is coming from Paytm Payment Bank, so the
stock rate of Paytm will
remain at RBI has given permission to
appoint Surendra Chawla as MD and CEO, he
will hold the post for the next 3 years, he is
actually the
branch
banking branch head of RBL, his focus was to
expand the business base, then increase the avenue,
cross selling, cross channel, that was, he has done it
in HDFC also, so a
good special  It is
seen to be getting linked with experience, so some
positives will come for Paytm
and of course there is an update on IDBI Bank as well,
Manicontrol.com has an exclusive
that Emirates MBD and Prem Badshah's
Fav Facts Group have actually
emerged as interested parties,
they have bid for IDBI Bank
and remember the government and LIC together will be
seen offloading around 67-60% stock,
coincidentally CSB Bank is in the
hands of both the resale controlling tech factors,
so Fav has experience of
investing in the bank, you will see whether
their name gets finalized with IDBI Bank or
not.